Under Jujutsu regulations, Itadori Yuuji,
I will exorcise you as a curse!
Wait, really, I'm just fine!
More importantly, you and I
are both pretty beat up.
Let's get to a hospital.
I can't tell if the one speaking right now
is Itadori or the cursed object...
Damn it! What should I do?!
What's the situation?
Gojou-sensei?! Why are you here?
Hey.
I wasn't planning on coming,
but man, you're roughed up.
I should show the second-years.
Face this way.
The higher-ups wouldn't shut up with a
special-grade cursed object gone missing.
So I stopped by while
doing some sightseeing.
So, did you find it?
Um...
Sorry, but I ate it.
For real?
For real.
Damn, it really did combine with you.
That's hilarious.
Anything off with your body?
Not particularly.
Can you swap out with Sukuna?
Sukuna?
The curse you ate.
Oh... Yeah, I think I can do that.
Then give us ten seconds.
Once ten seconds are up, come back to us.
But...
Don't worry, I'm the strongest.
Megumi, hold on to this.
What is it?
Kikufuku from Kikusuian.
Kikufuku
It's Sendai's specialty, and it's super good.
I recommend the zunda and cream flavor.
This guy actually went and bought souvenirs!
When people were out here dying!
It's not a souvenir.
I'm going to eat it on the bullet train home.
Behind you!
Kikufuku's not like other souvenirs...
And the whipped cream
inside is simply exquisite...
My student's watching,
so I'm going to show off a little.
He's unbelievably fast?
No, that's not it...
For crying out loud...
You jujutsu sorcerers are always trouble,
no matter what the era!
Though that doesn't mean much to me.
Seven...
Eight...
Nine...
Should be time.
Damn it... Again?
I can't take over.
Who the hell is this... Itadori... brat?
Oh, was everything okay?
I'm shocked.
You really can control it.
He's kind of annoying, though.
I can hear his voice.
It's a miracle that's all he's doing.
What did you do?
Knocked him out.
If he isn't possessed by
Sukuna when he wakes up,
he might have potential as a vessel.
Now, I have a question for you.
What should we do with him?
Even if he is a vessel,
jujutsu regulations demand
Itadori be executed.
However...
I don't want to let him die.
Your personal feelings?
Yes. Please do something about this.
Now it's a request from a precious student.
Leave it to me!
With that, allow me to say it once more.
You're being executed.
The recap and current
events don't line up, though.
Hey, I did my best.
The execution's still on,
but I got your sentence suspended.
Suspended?
So you're not killing me right away?
Yup.
I'll explain from the top.
This is the same as the cursed object you ate.
There are twenty in total.
We possess six of them.
Twenty?
Oh, each finger and toe?
No, Sukuna has four arms.
As you can see, we can't destroy them.
The curse is just that powerful.
The curse grows stronger by the day,
and the seals of modern-day
jujutsu sorcerers can't keep up.
That's where you come in.
When you die, the curse
inside you will die, as well.
Our elders are cowards, you know.
They're demanding we kill you right away.
But that would be a waste, wouldn't it?
A waste?
There's no guarantee another vessel capable
of handling Sukuna will ever be born again.
So this is what I proposed:
If we're going to kill you anyway,
why not kill you after you've
absorbed all of Sukuna?
The higher-ups agreed.
So now you have two options before you.
You can die right now,
or you can find all the parts of Sukuna
and die after you've absorbed them.
Jujutsu Kaisen
Sugisawa Hospital
Episode 2:         For Myself
Itadori.
How's Iguchi-senpai doing?
The doctors say he's fine,
but he hasn't regained consciousness.
It's all my fault.
If I hadn't asked him to come
to the school that night...
I know you won't believe this,
but this weird monster attacked us,
and I was captured, too.
I believe you.
Those weren't monsters. They were curses.
That finger was a special-grade cursed object.
It had the power to draw other
curses to it and make them stronger.
So it wasn't your fault.
It was mine for picking it up.
Sorry.
It'll be all right, though.
Someone capable of fixing
Iguchi-senpai will be here tomorrow.
Itadori?
Sorry, Senpai.
There's somewhere I need to go.
Bye-bye.
Who passed away?
My grandpa. Although he
was like a father to me.
I see. Sorry it happened at a time like that.
So have you decided what you want to do?
Are casualties like these
from curses pretty common?
This one was a rather exceptional case,
but in terms of the damage,
it happens all the time.
It's a good night when someone dies
a normal death after encountering a curse.
Finding a body that's all torn apart
is on the better end of the outcomes.
If you plan to hunt down Sukuna,
you're going to witness some gruesome scenes,
and I can't guarantee you
won't end up that way yourself.
So choose your hell.
You're a strong kid, so help others.
If all the parts of Sukuna were gone,
would there be fewer people
who get harmed by curses?
Of course.
Do you still have that finger?
Looking at it again, it's pretty disgusting.
Well, that's the second one.
One tenth of the whole.
What's going to happen?
Gross!
So gross it's funny.
That settles it.
It's not just a physical tolerance.
He can control himself
against Sukuna without issue.
We haven't seen someone with
talent like that in a thousand years.
Something wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
I take it this means you've
steeled your resolve?
Not at all.
I'm still wondering why
I have to be executed.
But I can't just do nothing about the curse.
That last request is gonna be a pain in my ass.
I'll eat every part of Sukuna.
I don't care what happens from there.
I've already decided how I'm going to die.
Nice! I like people like you.
Sounds like a fun hell awaits.
Make sure you're packed
by the end of the day.
We going somewhere?
Tokyo.
Fushiguro! You're looking good!
You think so after seeing this?
You're going to transfer to the same
school for jujutsu sorcerers I attend.
Huh?
Tokyo Metropolitan Jujutsu
Technical High School.
By the way, you're the third first-year.
Only three?!
Okay, I'm heading out, Grandpa.
Itadori Family Grave
This is really deep in the mountains!
Is this actually Tokyo?
Even Tokyo's like this on the outskirts.
Where's Fushiguro?
He's been treated by a sorcerer,
and now he's fast asleep.
Tokyo Metropolitan Jujutsu
Technical High School.
Tokyo Metropolitan
Jujutsu Technical High School
It's one of only two jujutsu
educational facilities.
On the surface, it's known
as a private religious school.
Many jujutsu sorcerers continue
to use it as a base after graduation,
so it's a pillar of the jujutsu community
not just in education, but for
support and mediation in missions.
Anyway, you're about to have
an interview with the principal.
The principal?
Screw it up and he could reject
your admission, so go all-out.
Huh?!
And what then? Immediate execution?!
What?
So you're not the boss?
Any hierarchy other
than strength is worthless.
Sorry, Sensei.
He pops out sometimes.
What an amusing body you have now.
I owe you a favor, you know.
Not again!
Once I make this brat's body my own,
you'll be the first one I kill!
It's an honor to be targeted by Sukuna.
This guy's really that famous?
Ryoumen Sukuna is a fierce imaginary
god with four arms and two faces.
But he's actually a human that really existed,
though it was over a thousand years ago.
In the golden age of jujutsu,
sorcerers gathered up all their might
to challenge him and failed.
Crowned with the title of Sukuna,
we couldn't even destroy his grave wax
as he traversed the ages
after death as a cursed object.
Without a doubt, he is the king of curses.
Who's stronger, you or him?
Well...
If Sukuna regained all of his power,
it might be a little draining.
Would you lose?
I'd win.
You're late, Satoru.
Eight minutes late.
Not enough to chastise you for,
but I know I told you to fix
your habit of being late.
That old dude's making cute things!
If it's not enough to chastise me for,
then don't chastise me.
You're just making dolls, anyway.
What's a measly eight minutes?
That's Principal Yaga Masamichi.
That's the boy?
Itadori Yuuji!
I'm into girls like Jennifer Lawrence!
Pleasure to meet you!
What did you come here for?
An interview.
But why Jujutsu Tech?
To learn jujutsu?
I mean beyond that.
What do you hope to find once you've studied
curses and learned how to exorcise them?
Well, I mean... I'm going to
collect the fingers of Sukuna.
It's dangerous to just leave them as is.
Why?
People you'll never know
die every day due to crimes,
accidents, and diseases
in the natural course of life.
Here he goes again.
But you're telling me you can't overlook it
when that death is caused by a curse?
It was someone's dying wish.
I don't care about the details.
I just want to save people.
A dying wish?
So you're saying you'll fight against curses
because someone else told you to?
You fail.
Those weren't dolls?!
Cursed corpses. They're dolls.
Dolls infused with my curse.
It's heavy!
Is that really a doll?!
A person's true nature
reveals itself during a crisis.
I'll keep attacking you until
I get an acceptable answer.
Look, man, it wasn't just "someone else."
It was a family member's dying wish!
Shit, where is it?!
Ow...
A family member is still "someone else."
Right, it's a doll.
It doesn't get hurt or frightened.
A jujutsu sorcerer is
constantly facing death.
And not just their own death.
Sometimes you must ignore those murdered
by a curse to rend the flesh from it.
It's an unpleasant job.
You have to be a little crazy
and highly motivated to handle it.
You'd do that because
someone else told you to?
Don't make me laugh.
It'd be more believable if you told me you
were doing it to postpone your execution.
Screw you! I—
Are you going to blame your grandfather
when you're killed by a curse, too?
You say some pretty damn
harsh things, old man.
Education is making people realize things.
I'm not really...
It's not easy to imagine how
you'll feel on the verge of death.
However, I can say one thing for certain.
At the rate you're going, you could end
up cursing your beloved grandfather.
Jujutsu sorcerers never die without regret.
I'll ask you once more.
Why have you come here to Jujutsu Tech?
I was always better than
most in sports and in fights.
But never once did I think,
"This is something only I can do."
Consuming Sukuna is something only I can do.
If I managed to escape my death sentence
and ran away from this responsibility,
I'd be there eating food,
taking a bath, or reading manga,
and the moment I stopped to think, I'd go,
"Oh, I bet someone's dying because of
Sukuna right now," and become depressed.
"That doesn't involve me."
"It's not my fault."
You expect me to just tell myself that?
I refuse to do that.
I don't know how I'll feel when I'm dying,
but I don't want to regret the way I lived!
Satoru.
Show him to the dorm.
Explain the security and
everything else to him, too.
Huh?
You pass.
Welcome to Jujutsu Tech.
Oh, sorry.
I forgot to release the curse.
This place is huge!
All the second- and third-years
are out at the moment.
Hello!
But you'll meet them soon enough.
Is anybody home?
There aren't many of them.
But there's really no reason
for you to fight, too, is there?
Fushiguro and I could
retrieve Sukuna's fingers.
You could just wait here.
It's fine! I said I'd do it, and I'm doing it!
Though lazing around...
Hey.
...while Fushiguro came in all beaten up
to bring me a finger would be a funny sight.
That's true.
Well, I know there's no way
in hell you're not gonna fight.
Hey! You were testing me?!
If they were that easy to find,
we would've found them all already.
Some have a presence that's overwhelming.
Some keep very quiet.
Some have already been
absorbed by a cursed spirit.
There's nothing more troublesome
when it comes to searching for them.
But now we have you.
The Sukuna within you will tell us where
the fingers are to try to regain his power.
You're both vessel and locator,
our very own radar.
So we won't get anywhere
without you in the field.
You think he's going to be that nice?
I think we can come to a
win-win agreement there.
You're next door?
Oh, Fushiguro!
You look like you're doing well now.
There were plenty other
empty rooms, weren't there?
But isn't livelier better?
I thought it'd be good for—
Classes and missions are enough.
This was an unwelcome favor.
Wow, it's so organized.
I just said you're unwelcome!
Well, it's all good.
More importantly, we're heading out tomorrow!
We're gonna go pick up the third first-year.
The train bound for Tokyo is now arriving.
For your safety, please
stand behind the yellow line.
It took four hours just
to get as far as Morioka.
I can finally kiss that
damn countryside goodbye.
Guess I'll be in Tokyo by the afternoon.
What should I do if I get scouted?
Like, by Stardust?
Episode 3:
Girl of Steel